A Guide to the Cocke Family Papers 1800-1871
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 August 14 (Box 4)
- M. F. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 August 21 (Box 4)
- H. M. Stribling to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1832 August 27] (Box 4)
- A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1832] August 28 (Box 4)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1832] September 5 (Box 4)
- M. L. Barraud to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 September 8 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 September 13 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 September 21 (Box 4)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 October 7 (Box 4)
- Susan J. Maxwell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1832 October 8 (Box 4)
- Mary P. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 October 8 (Box 4)
- M. P. Robertson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 October 15 (Box 4)
- A. B. Cabell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1832 November 2 (Box 4)
- A. B. Cabell to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1832 November 4 (Box 4)
- S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 November 5 (Box 4)
- S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 November 8 (Box 4)
- A. B. Cabell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1832 November 26 (Box 4)
- Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 December 1 (Box 4)
- C. E. Bowdoin to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1832 December 4 (Box 4)
- Susan W. Hartman to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1832 December 8 (Box 4)
- [Mrs.] D. A. Hurd to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1832 December 14 (Box 4)
- Miss S. F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1832 December] (Box 4)
- Miss S. F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1832 December] (Box 4)
- Virginia Cary to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1833 January 1 (Box 4)
- [Miss] P[arke F.]; C[arter] to Miss Lucy W. Oliver 1833 January 25 (Box 4)
- [Miss] P[arke][F.] C[arter] to Miss Lucy W. Oliver 1833 March 29 (Box 4)
- Mr. Cary C. Cocke to Miss Lucy Oliver 1833 May 17 (Box 4)
- Miss [Susan] J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1833 June 14 (Box 4)
- [Miss] Susan J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1833 June 20 (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1833 July 5 (Box 4)
- Mrs. A. Barraud to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1833 July [9] (Box 4)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 July 23 (Box 4)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 August 6 (Box 5)
- Mrs. P. R. [Margaret] Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 August 13 (Box 5)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 August 15 (Box 5)
- C. Bowdoin to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1833 August 19 (Box 5)
- Miss A. C. C[oleman] to Miss Lucy Oliver 1833 August 19 (Box 5)
- Mrs. P. R. [Margaret] Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1833] August 23 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Margaret Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 August 26 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 October 8 (Box 5)
- Miss S. J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 October 16 (Box 5)
- S. F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 October 16 (Box 5)
- Miss S[usan] J. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 October 23 (Box 5)
- Rev. Shepard K. Kollock to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1833] December 21 (Box 5)
- Miss Ann B. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1833 November (Box 5)
- Miss A. C. Coleman to Miss Lucy Oliver 1833 (Box 5)
- Miss P[arke F.]; C[arter] to Miss Lucy Oliver 1833 (Box 5)
- [Miss] P[arke F.]; C[arter] to Miss Lucy Oliver 1834 April 23 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1834 May 16 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1834 May 20 (Box 5)
- A. B. [Cabell] to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1834 May 25 (Box 5)
- Mr. Wm. M. Atkinson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1834 July 29 (Box 5)
- Miss Ann C. Coleman to Miss Lucy Oliver 1834 August 11 (Box 5)
- H. C. Harrison (Mrs. R., Jr.) to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1834 August 14 (Box 5)
- S. J. Harrison to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1834 August 16 (Box 5)
- Miss A. C. Coleman to Miss Lucy Oliver 1834 September 29 (Box 5)
- S[allie] B. C[ocke] to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1834] November 3 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. A. Pool to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1834], [1824] November 17 (Box 5)
- Mr. William L. White to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1834 December 24 (Box 5)
- S[allie] B. C[ocke] to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] 1834 November (Box 5)
- A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1834 November (Box 5)
- Miss A. C. C[oleman] to Miss Lucy Oliver 1834 (Box 5)
- A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1834] (Box 5)
- A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke [1834] (Box 5)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. [Louisa] Cocke 1835 December 25 (Box 5)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1836 January 1-November 22 (Box 5)
- General John H. Cocke to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1836 August 22 (Box 5)
- Diary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1836 November 22-1837 April 20 (Box 5)
- Miss P[arke F.]; C[arter] to Miss Lucy Oliver 1836 (Box 5)
- Bill; Charles Ellie to General John H. Cocke 1837 October 14 (Box 5)
- Miss P[arke F.] Carter to Miss Lucy Oliver 1837 December 18 (Box 5)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1837 April 22- December 30 (Box 5)
- Mr. Charles Carter to Mr. Cary C. Cocke 1837 (Box 5)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 1- November 8 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 3 (Box 5)
- Mrs. A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 26 (Box 5)
- Rev. Daniel B. Woods to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 January 31 (Box 5)
- Miss Mary Slaughter to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 12 (Box 5)
- Andrew Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 13 (Box 5)
- Mrs. M. L. Barraud to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 16 (Box 5)
- Dr. G. P. Holeman to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 17 (Box 5)
- Miss Caroline Towles to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 20 (Box 5)
- N. F. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 February 22 (Box 5)
- Andrew Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 March 16 (Box 5)
- Miss Hannah Carroll to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 March 28 (Box 5)
- M. F. R. to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 March (Box 5)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 5 (Box 5)
- G. M. Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 5 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 7 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. I. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 7 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Courtney Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 10 (Box 10)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 12 (Box 5)
- Miss Ann Gray to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 19 (Box 5)
- Mrs. A. M. Rivers to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 27 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 27 (Box 5)
- Mrs. M. L. Barraud to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 April 30 (Box 5)
- Miss Diana Skipwith to Louisana Cocke 1838 May 8 (Box 5)
- Rev. Daniel B. Woods to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 May 10 (Box 5)
- Mrs. H. C. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 May 12 (Box 5)
- Mrs. H. C. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 May 20 (Box 5)
- Miss Ann Gray to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 May 21 (Box 5)
- Mrs. A. B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 May (Box 5)
- R. T. Archer to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 3 (Box 5)
- Mrs. P. St. G. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 4 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. I. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 7 (Box 5)
- Miss Harriette Burr to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 9 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 12 (Box 5)
- R. T. Archer to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 15 (Box 5)
- Rev. Daniel B. Woods to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 16 (Box 5)
- George Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 26 (Box 5)
- Francis H. Smith to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 June 28 (Box 5)
- Miss Ann Gray to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 2 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Augusta Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 4 (Box 5)
- W. M. Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 8 (Box 5)
- Mrs. A. M. Rives to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 8 (Box 8)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. I. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 July 20 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. A. Poole to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 August 3 (Box 5)
- R. W. Tomlin to Miss Lucy W. Oliver 1838 August 4 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 August 7 (Box 5)
- John B. Hart to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 August 13 (Box 5)
- W. M. Wilson to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 August 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 August 23 (Box 5)
- Sally Faulcon Cocke to Miss Lucy W. Oliver 1838 September 3 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. I. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 September 11 (Box 11)
- C. B. Scott to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 September 12 (Box 5)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 September 29 (Box 5)
- Miss Sally F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 8 (Box 5)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 11 (Box 5)
- Mrs. M. C. Sims to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 11 (Box 5)
- John H. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 15 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. I. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 October 18 (Box 5)
- Mrs. Mary B. Strange to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 1 (Box 5)
- Miss Mary E. Terrell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 2 (Box 5)
- Mr. A. B. Barraud to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 6 (Box 5)
- Mr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 8 (Box 5)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 9- 1839 September 25 (Box 5)
- Mrs. S. W. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 16 (Box 5)
- Mr. S. H. Trokes to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 16 (Box 5)
- Rev. S. W. Blain to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 20 (Box 5)
- Mr. A. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 November 25 (Box 5)
- Miss Sally F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 December 1 (Box 6)
- Miss Sally F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 December 5 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 December 18 (Box 6)
- Mrs. S. G. Harrison to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 December 20 (Box 6)
- S. F. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1838 December 27 (Box 6)
- Miss Lucy Oliver to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1838 (Box 6)
- Miss Lucy Oliver to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1838 (Box 6)
- Daniel B. Woods to John H. Cocke, Jr. 1839 January 28 (Box 6)
- Mrs. A. Randolph to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1839 September 12 (Box 6)
- ______ Braxton to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1839 September 20 (Box 6)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1839 September 29- 1840 June 9 (Box 6)
- Miss P[arke F.] C[arter] to Miss Luch Oliver 1839 (Box 6)
- Mrs. I. H. Coulter to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1840 May 21 (Box 6)
- John Cowan to Cary C. Cocke 1840 June 25 (Box 6)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1840 June 10-December 31 (Box 6)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1841 January 1- August 24 (Box 6)
- Diary of Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1841 August 25- 1842 August 28 (Box 6)
- Bill; Robb, Winebrener & Co. to John H. Cocke, Jr. 1841 December 31 (Box 6)
- Ann Gray to Mrs. P. St. G. Cocke 1842 January 6 (Box 6)
- Miss Bal Barnes to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1842 May 15 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1842 December 14 (Box 6)
- M. W. Braxton to Mrs. Charles Cocke 1843 January 4 (Box 6)
- Miss Nannie Oliver to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 January 9 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 February 3 (Box 6)
- M. W. Braxton to Mrs. Charles Cocke 1843 March 6 (Box 6)
- Miss Ann (Nannie) B. Oliver to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 March 20 (Box 6)
- M. W. Braxton to Mrs. Charles C. Cocke 1843 March 27 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 May 23 (Box 6)
- Mrs. P. St. G. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 June 9 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Charles Cocke 1843 July 10 (Box 6)
- Miss A. Braxton to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1843 July 26 (Box 6)
- Mrs. P. St. G. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1843 August 7 (Box 6)
- Miss Sarah _____ to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1843 September 11 (Box 6)
- Mr. [A.] Braxton to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1843 October 29 (Box 6)
- Mr. [A.] Braxton to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1843 November 1 (Box 6)
- Wm. Pollock to General J. H. Cocke 1843 November 7 (Box 6)
- Miss Nannie Oliver to Mrs. Dr. Charles Cocke 1844 March 4 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1844 March 27 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1844 April 8 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Charles Cocke 1844 May 8 (Box 6)
- Miss Margaret Barnes to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1844 May 25 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1844 June 17 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1844 July 24 (Box 6)
- Miss P[arke F.] Carter to Lucy Oliver 1844 August 4 (Box 6)
- Mr. [A.] Braxton to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1845 January 18 (Box 6)
- Mr. [A.] Braxton to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1845 February 18 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Cary C. Cocke to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1845 June 11 (Box 6)
- Miss Bal Barnes to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1845 July 10 (Box 6)
- Miss Bal Barnes to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1846 January 29 (Box 6)
- Cary C. Cocke to Miss Lucy F. Cocke 1847 December 3 (Box 6)
- Mr. John H. Cocke to Mrs. Sally F. Cocke 1847 (Box 6)
- General John H. Cocke's Sons of Temperance Certificate 1848 October 28 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1850 July 10 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Miss Sally F. Cocke 1850 September 7 (Box 6)
- M. W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1850 October 26 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1850 November 6 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1850 December 21 (Box 6)
- Miss Olivia _____ to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1851 December 27 (Box 6)
- Mary Maxwell to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1852 February 18 (Box 6)
- Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. [Lucy] Cocke 1852 May 16 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1852 May 18 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke 1852 May 25 (Box 6)
- R. W. Tomlin to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1853 August 7 (Box 6)
- M. D. [Holt] to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1854 October 19 (Box 6)
- S. B. Jones to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1856 January 28 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Cary C. Cocke to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1856 November 19 (Box 6)
- Miss Kate ____ to Miss Nannie C. Cocke 1857 August 13 (Box 6)
- Lucy F. Braxton to Miss Nannie C Oliver 1859 October 30 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1859 November 20 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Cary C. Cocke to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1860 June 30 (Box 6)
- "Broadsides", Merchants' and Planters' Prices-Current 1860 October 27 (Box 6)
- "Broadsides", Black Hawk and Post Boy 1861 April 1 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Sally Faulcon Brent to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1861 April 13 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Wm. P. Munford to Miss Bal Barnes 1861 May 27 (Box 6)
- Lucy J. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1861 May 31 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Cary C. Cocke to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1861 October 29 (Box 6)
- General John H. Cocke to John H. Cocke, III 1861 December 2 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 March 9 (Box 6)
- General John H. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 March 10 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 March 11 (Box 6)
- Miss Lucy C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 March 16 (Box 6)
- Lucy J. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 May 13 (Box 6)
- F. C. Young to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1864 July 5 (Box 6)
- Mrs. Mary C. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 July 14 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 August 5 (Box 6)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 September 14 (Box 6)
- Mary Maxwell to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 September 19 (Box 6)
- John Hartwell Cocke, III to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1864 October 10 (Box 6)
- John H. Cocke, III to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1864 October 12 (Box 6)
- John H. Cocke, III to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1864 October 20 (Box 6)
- F. C. Young to Miss Nannie C. Oliver [1864] October 21 (Box 6)
- John H. Cocke, III to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 October 25 (Box 6)
- Lucy T. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 November 28 (Box 6)
- Braxton ____ to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1864 November 29 (Box 6)
- Lucy T. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 December 9 (Box 6)
- Mary W. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1864 December 14 (Box 6)
- [R. H. Baker] to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1865 January 23 (Box 7)
- R. H. Baker to Dr. Cary C. Cocke 1865 January 24 (Box 7)
- Lucy T. Braxton to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke 1865 February 20 (Box 7)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Col. _____ 1865 March 23 (Box 7)
- Dr. Cary C. Cocke to Dr. Wm. H. McGuffey 1866 July 31, Copy (Box 7)
- John H. Cocke, III to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1868 January 24 (Box 7)
- E. & S. Wortham & Co. to Miss Nannie C. Oliver 1871 March 10 (Box 7)
- Dr. Charles H. Cocke to Mrs. W. B. Shields 1925 March 18 (Box 7)
- Cary C. Cocke to Miss Nannie C. Oliver _____ January 13 (Box 7)
- Miss Nannie Oliver to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke _____ February 13 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Lucy Baker to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke _____ March 10 (Box 7)
- A. E. Johns to Dr. & Mrs. Cary C. Cocke _____ March 20 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Louisa Cocke to her son Charles C. Cocke _____ March 20 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Cary C. Cocke ______ March 20 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Louisa Cocke to Cary C. Cocke _____ April 17 (Box 7)
- Miss Bal Barnes to Miss Nannie C. Oliver ____ May 22 (Box 7)
- Miss Bal Barnes to Miss Nannie C. Oliver _____ May 30 (Box 7)
- Benj. E. Payne to Mrs. Louisa Holmes _____ June 3 (Box 7)
- A. B. Cabell to [Mrs. Louisa Cocke] _____ July 23 (Box 7)
- Sally F. Cocke to Charles Cary Cocke _____ August 2 (Box 7)
- Mrs. James Maxwell to Mrs. Louisa Holmes _____ August 3 (Box 7)
- John Maxwell to Miss Louisa Maxwell _____September 25 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Dr. Cary C. Cocke _____ October 13 (Box 7)
- Mrs. P. St. G. Cocke to Mrs. Louisa Cocke _____ November 28 (Box 7)
- Mrs. Ann B. Cabell to Mrs. Louisa Cocke _____ December 10 (Box 7)
- Miss Lelia Bryan to Miss Nannie C. Oliver ______ December (Box 7)
- Mrs. William Galt to Mrs. Louisa Cocke n.d. (Box 7)
- Mrs. Virginia Cary to Mrs. Louisa Cocke n.d. (Box 7)
- F. D. Moncure to Miss Nannie C. Oliver n.d. (Box 7)
- Mary Maxwell to Miss Nannie C. Oliver n.d. (Box 7)
- M. Barnes to Miss Ann (Nannie) B. Oliver n.d. (Box 7)
- Last Pages n.d. (Box 7)
- Poetry written to Miss Nannie C. Oliver n.d. (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Papers n.d. (Box 7)
- Dates from Cocke family Bibles and Genealogy n.d. (Box 7)
- Short Sketch of Life of John H. Cocke 1780-1866 (Box 7)
- Copies of letters from Thomas Jefferson, James Madison and Lafayette to General John H. Cocke n.d. (Box 7)
- Report of Mazyok W. Shields on the operation of Bremo Farm 1926 (Box 7)
- J.H. Cocke, Chronology and Contemporaries n.d., 3 x 5 cards